[Music]
good morning everyone this week started
with heavy snowfall and plummeting
temperatures which can be a little
challenging but also natural part of
winter life in my Valley today I'm going
to the grocery store to get some food
for the week which is always a little
Adventure on the rural icy
[Music]
roads
ready go go
[Music]
on
once I got back it was time to let my
rabbits out in their play pen which is
their absolute favorite part of the day
and I have to admit they're looking so
cute with their thick winter
coats noing my
shoelaces in this video I wanted to
share with you something that I've come
to realize I need to work on in
2024 it's not a problem everyone can
relate to but it is something I've set
my mind on improving this year and I
think at least some aspects of it are
relevant to most souls and that is that
when it comes to certain things in life
I struggle to trust myself and it's an
interesting challenge to face because it
can manifest in many ways for example I
often let other people in my life make
decisions for me because I don't trust
myself to make the right one I'm afraid
of my own decisions because I'm afraid
I'll fail somehow and it will be my
fault I sometimes ruminate over things I
said in the past worrying that my
intentions were misinterpreted or that I
accidentally hurt someone not trusting
myself to have done the best I could in
the moment and being at peace with
that
[Music]
I often question my own intuition
especially in regard to friendships
someone may not treat me respectfully
and yet I'll not trust my interpretation
of events and instead make excuses for
them time and again often putting myself
in the position of being a pushover
afraid to speak my
[Music]
mind
recently I tried to take a big step
forward on this journey and set a very
important boundary with a longtime
acquaintance this person had a tendency
to make fun of me in public when I made
a mistake and while for years I'd never
addressed it and just convinced myself
it was their sense of humor and I didn't
want to make a fuss I finally shared
that it was hurting me I made a simple
request but it was so hard for me to do
but I had grown enough to think that I
deserve to receive the same kindness I
wanted to give and that my point was
valid I decided to trust myself and act
sadly that person got very defensive and
our relationship hasn't been the same
sense this was my worst fear coming true
and a part of me just wanted to take
back all I said I decided to try not to
turn my back on this journey of self
trust accepting that that does mean that
sometimes relationships change and I
need to grow stronger in my sense of
self so I can know I have value even if
someone is upset with
[Music]
me
if I'm completely honest I do not trust
that I will be kind to myself when I
most need to be I think perhaps many of
you have this tendency too for example I
may say I'm afraid of failure but in
reality I'm not I am afraid of how I
will treat myself if I fail I may be
afraid to make a big decision but I'm
more afraid that I'll be critical and
unkind to myself if I make the wrong one
in reality failures and mistakes are
natural parts of life if I let it
undermine my sense of self of trust and
confidence in who I am I willingly give
away all my
power I really want to spend as little
time is possible this year living in
fear of myself I want to be my best
friend and now I'm trying to do just
[Music]
that
sitting
[Music]
down
to end the day I decided to go out into
the Twilight light and light some
candles making a little promise to
myself that from this day forward I will
work on developing my courage and
becoming who I was meant to be perhaps
it's time you make this promise to
yourself either way I appreciate you
being here and I'm sending you all my
love for a beautiful
[Music]
year
hello everyone I hope you enjoyed this
video I have been working on it for a
while so it was really lovely to share
it with you and I appreciate all your
advice and insight and I hope that at
least the topic of this video is one
that some of you can relate it's
definitely something I'm really trying
to change this year about myself uh it's
something very important that I realized
was affecting my life in a way that
wasn't helping me move forward I have no
doubt I will make significant progress
this year and I hope that if you are on
a similar Journey that you know I'm
sending you all the encouragement and
support I also wanted to let you all
know that I finally reopened my Etsy
Shop it has taken a little while but it
is open now and I have the cottage
bookmarks back in stock so they look
like this and on the back they say
dreaming of a little cottage in the
woods and I really like how they turned
out so I have matching bookmarks my Etsy
Shop makes it possible for me to make
videos so I really appreciate those who
are supportive of that endeavor but
there's never any obligation to being
here is more than enough I do have some
sad news though I will no longer be able
to do international shipping as of the
start of February this is because my
little post office is under staffed
right now currently to send
International packages I have to drive a
very long way to find a post office that
can uh help me and so it's just been a
huge undertaking and I've decided that
it's just too much to be doing so I will
be open an international orders for
another couple weeks and I appreciate
your understanding unfortunately I'm not
in the position to be doing intern naal
labels and printing and all that at home
and I do rely on the post office so I'm
just making do with the circumstances
thank you again for all your love and
kindness and I'm wishing you a
absolutely wonderful week sending you so
much love and I will see you soon
[Music]
goodbye